onerx.in 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy

      OneRX is retail one stop shop for Health & Beauty. OneRx vision of  having chain of modern trade retails outlets across pan India. In general, you visit OneRx.in estore without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you. At OneRx.in protecting your privacy is most important we do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances.

1\. **Personally Identifiable Information We Collect About You.  **

We gather information that is necessary to complete your orders for our products and services. On the pages at our website where you can order medications, make requests, or ask questions, we collect personal information from you, typically:

Name, address, phone number, email address, and other personal contact information

Name and contact information of your physician

Prescription information on the medications requested

Credit card and shipping information

**2.Why We Collect The Personal Information:  **

The choice to provide us with your personal information is not mandatory but not supplying these particular details may limit the products and services we are able to provide you and make it more difficult for us to advise you or suggest appropriate alternatives.   
We use the information that we collect on our Web sites to provide you with a superior shopping experience and to communicate with you about products, services, and promotions. 

**3.The Way We Collect:  **

We use the information you provide when placing an order only to complete the order. We do not share this information with any outside third parties, except to the extent necessary to complete the order.  
We also use the personal information provided by you to communicate with you. We use the return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such email addresses are not used for any other purposes and are not shared with any outside parties.  
We use non-identifying information for statistical purposes and to enhance the usefulness of our website. We never use or share the personal information provided to us on line in ways unrelated to the ones described above without your consent or providing you an opportunity to opt out. 

**4.Our Commitment to Privacy:  **

We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We maintain information on the contact history that is used for responding to customer inquires and to complete medication refill requests.  
If we cannot deliver the services requested of us because of the lack of necessary information, we may ask for additional information on a case-by-case basis.  
We may collect non-identifying information, that is, information that cannot be traced to or associated with a specific individual or business entity. The choice to provide us with any personal information is always yours.

**5.Our Commitment To Data Security:  **

Your personal information and credit card or debit card information are encrypted using (Secure Sockets Layer) SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. We use SSL technology to prevent your information from being stolen or intercepted while being transferred to us and once we have received it. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a restricted-access database that is away from our Web site database so it is not connected to the Internet, to keep it safe from hackers.  
Only the last 4 digits of your credit card are reflected in our database thus even our support operators do not have any access to the credit card information.  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**6.How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  **

You can access or correct any factual errors in all your personal identifiable information that we collect online by sending us a request to do so. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or correcting errors. 

**7\. Compliance with law:  **

Protection of Rights, Property or Safety - We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or legal process served on us; and/or to protect our rights and the rights of our customers; or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other policies or user agreements. 

  1. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with OneRx.inunder extremely strict confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help OneRx.in communicate with you about offers from OneRx.inand our marketing partners. These companies(eg. Google, promotional emailing etc) may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  2. We do collect personal information like your name ,mail id, address, age, medical records over the phone to meet your needs when you make a call on the IVR. These calls are recorded on our server and on the server of third party who are service provider to us. Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.  Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. OneRx.inis not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party.
  3. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.
  4. We transfer information about you if OneRx.inis acquired by or merged with another company.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name and address or email id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to download our white papers or to provide you with a subscription. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested.

**Users Note:**

   I.        As part of the registration/application creation and submission process that is available to Users on this website, certain information, including sensitive personal data or information is collected from the Users.

   II.        All the statements in this privacy policy apply to all Users, and all Users are therefore required to read and understand the privacy statements set out herein prior to submitting any sensitive personal data or information to OneRX, failing which they are required to leave this Website immediately.

   III.        **If you have inadvertently submitted any such information to  ** **OneRX** **  prior to reading the privacy statements set out herein**, and you do not agree with the manner in which such information is collected, stored or used, then you may access, modify and delete all information stored about You byOneRX by clicking on the "Edit Profile". In addition, any User can ask OneRX, by sending an email to info@OneRX.com whether OneRX is keeping personal data about him/her, and every User is also entitled to require OneRXto delete and destroy all such information relating to him/her (but not other Users) in its possession.

  IV.        Users' personally identifiable information they choose to provide on the Website is used to help the Users describe / identify themselves. Other information that does not personally identify the Users as an individual, is collected by OneRX from Users (such as, patterns of utilization described above) and is exclusively owned by OneRX. OneRX may also use such information in an aggregated or non-personally identifiable form for research, statistical analysis and business intelligence purposes, and may sell or otherwise transfer such research, statistical or intelligence data in an aggregated or non-personally identifiable form to third parties and affiliates. If OneRX wishes to use any User's personal data for a new purpose, it will seek such User's permission before doing so.

   V.        OneRX will communicate with the Users through email and notices posted on the Website or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. The Users can change their e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into their "Account" at www.OneRX.com and changing the account settings.

   VI.        All OneRX employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of sensitive personal data or information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of every User's sensitive personal data and information.

   VII. OneRX may also disclose or transfer User's personal and other information a User provides, to another third party as part of reorganization or a sale of the assets of a OneRX corporation division or company. Any third party to which OneRX transfers or sells its assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that a User provide to us.
